Number one, we measure and track.
Number two, we monitor and disrupt.
We have a whole apparatus.
I have 40 analysts working full-time,
seven days a week, 24 hours a day,
monitoring extremists.
We monitor them online,
social media,
messaging apps, video games,
cryptocurrency, podcasts,
short-form video, Wikipedia,
LLMs.
We monitor these people,
and we share the intelligence with the FBI.
You saw last month,
you heard about the thing that happened
at Wilshire Boulevard Temple.
Our analysts investigated what happened.
They said they were Koreatown for Palestine,
this group of people.
They weren't.
We were able to ascertain
they were from a group called
the Turtle Island Liberation Front.
Turtle Island is how left-wing activists
refer to the United States.
They don't call it America.
They call it Turtle Island,
like the Iranians call it,
Iranians call it the Zionist entity,
or they only call it by its name.
The Turtle Island Liberation Front,
we gave them a whole dossier.
Who are,
what is Turtle Island Liberation Front?
What are their ideas,
their goals?
Who are they?
We identified the people
who were in the synagogue.
This was on Wednesday,
December the 10th.
On Monday,
December the 15th,
this is going to ring a bell.
Kash Patel announced
they cracked a terror ring
where they arrested four people
who were playing New Year's Eve bombings.
Turtle Island Liberation Front.
At least one of the people
I know for certain
was in the building
at Wilshire Boulevard Temple
vandalizing it
and disrupting the event.
So we're monitoring
left-wing radicals
like the DSA
and the anti-war crazies
and the pro-Palestine crazies.
We're monitoring right-wing extremists
like white supremacists,
armed militia groups.
We're monitoring political Islamists
and Christian nationalists,
all of them.
And then we train.
We're the largest trainer
of law enforcement in America,
extremism hate.
We train 20,000 officers every year.